Darn.
Wow, I want to live here.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
I'm Hina Kawada from Hinatazaka46.
This time, we're going to take the second part of the Hina Walk,
Last time we went to Mt,
What will we do this time?
Cycling. Yay!
Why cycling?
I have a destination in mind.
What do you think it is?
That's right. It's a meal.
You know, I really like curry,
I would like to have curry in the morning.
I have never pedaled a bicycle in Tokyo,
I used to pedal in my hometown,
But I have never pedaled a bike since I moved here,
I am a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous, but I'm looking forward to enjoying my first bike ride.
Last time I started in the dark, but today the sun has already risen, so I'm going to enjoy my first bike ride,
But today, the sun has already risen,
I will enjoy the ride. I will enjoy it.
Well, let's get started!Well, let's get to it.
Today, my partner is already here.
Let me introduce you.
Ta-da!
So cute!
The color is perfect.
It's from Hinatazaka.
The group's color is sky blue.
It's sky blue.
I was with this girl today.
I'd like to spend a few hours
I'd like to spend some time with her.
I'd like to spend a few hours with her.
It feels good. Maybe it's the Tamagawa.
I'm happy. It's a lawn.
Is it a lawn?
It's cool. Biking is a lot cooler than walking.
Great.
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm.
Excuse me.
Passersby?
I mean, I think I'm going to make it a goal to say hello
I think I'm going to make it a goal to say hello just once.
I think I can do that.
Hello, sir.Hello.
I tried, but no response.
Maybe I'm being too modest, really.
You have to be imposing to get your message across.
She did respond a little bit.
I'm glad.
I mean, I saw his face.
He got attached to me.
Wow.
Maybe I'm feeling a little better.
I was fine.
I'm so happy to see you.
Let's talk about the 10th single.
Have you heard of IREBY?
If you haven't, please listen to it now.
It's a totally different story.
It looks like the road I used to walk to school in middle school.
I remember going this way in middle school.
It brings back memories.
I love the smell of grass.
I love the smell of wet earth and grass.
It's like Ghibli!
I forgot to mention this at the opening.
I'm running from Futakotamagawa to Tamagawa Zouki today.
I'm going to a curry shop in Tamagawa Zouki.So I'm going to a curry shop in the Tamaki area.
It's 20 kilometers away.
I don't know... 20 kilometers for cycling.
Is it less than you think? I wonder.
I only heard the distance.
I don't know what the standard is.
They all seem to be going at different speeds.
Why are they so fast?
Is it faster this way?
What's the difference?
I can't believe I'm halfway through!
I think we're about halfway through.
I'll take a break in a little while.
Oh, finally, we're over the halfway mark!
I'm so happy, but I'm surprised it's only halfway!
I'm going to eat some candy.
I was actually going to eat some sweets or something, but
but I'll try to eat it sparingly.
I didn't know it had a taste.
The other day, with Kumisan
And Uru-chan.
We had a cool game to see which way the candy was in.
This way.
We're always doing silly things like this backstage.
Yeah, it was really refreshing. We ate candy.Yeah, I felt really refreshed. I even ate some candy.
Curry. Curry.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Oh, there is a big bridge!
This is Sho-bashi bridge. We're going to cross it.
Red light.
I wonder if it's ready yet.
I forgot to push the button.
I forgot to push it. I've been waiting for so long.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm looking for this one, too.
Oh, wow.
We could shoot a music video.
Wow, I want to live here.
I want to live here!
Kawadashin is No. 1 on my wish list.
Because it's right in the heart of the city.
It's so calm.
It's nice.
It's so nice.
It feels like you're away from the city.
Wow, I don't know how to say it.
But it reminds me of my hometown.
It reminds me of when I went to different schools for ballet practice.I remember going to a ballet rehearsal at a different school.
Curry.
I'm almost ready to eat it now.
I'm so happy.
I really like curry. It's in the top three of my favorite foods.
Curry is by far my favorite food.
Or yakiniku. Yakiniku or curry.
I want to eat curry.
There's something about it that makes me feel like I'm about to go out on the town.
I can't wait to eat it. I can't wait to eat it. I can't wait to eat curry.
We're almost there.
I think my posture is starting to look like a pro.
You're leaning forward a little bit.
Like this... a professional cyclist.
Yes, a professional cyclist.
The bike path along the Hamagawa River has come to an end.
And we're almost at our destination.
I'm looking forward to it! Keep your eyes peeled.
Ah! Isn't this it?
Curry hamburger.
Over there! This one?
Curry and hamburger, second floor.
We're here! I'm so happy!
Well, we've arrived!
This time, we're going to visit Ska Cafe!This time we will be visiting Ska Cafe!
Curry & hamburgers, wow, I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, it looks like it's on the second floor... watch out!
I'm going to look forward to it.
Hello. Hello, I'm sorry to bother you.
Wow, it's cool.
Wow, it's so nice.
What a lot of things.
Superstars, too.
There are a lot of pictures and so on.
So cute!
Wow!
But it said hamburgers and curry
there is also a signboard below
There's hamburger steak curry.
Shall I get the cheese hamburger steak curry?
I'm greedy!
Cheese hamburger steak curry.
Yes, sir!
And a large banana juice, please.
Yes. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it. Waiting for food is my favorite time.
They start serving breakfast at 8:00 a.m. I'll have to get up early.
It's so cute. Thank you so much. It's so cute.
Beaker... what's the word?Beaker, what's the word, what's the word, it's a beaker, right?
It's cute. Bon appétit.
Delicious!
I'm glad I did it.
I worked so hard today for this.
Looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
It's a great big bloom, ladies and gentlemen.
Come on.
Who spills this kind of stuff?
There's sausage.
There's vegetables, all right.
It's hard to know where to start.
I'll start with the hamburger steak.
Wow, it's absolutely hot!
Wow, there's so much cheese!
Wow.
Yeah, it's hot.
Yeah, too hot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is my favorite hamburger. It's so meaty.
I'll have the curry, too.
You have to let it cool down before you eat it.
Yeah, it's delicious!Yeah, it's delicious.
Mmm! Delicious!
I heard it's medium spicy, so it's a little tangy.
But with this banana juice, it's really good!
See you in the next video!
Bye bye!
Mmmm, mmmm, hmmm, hmmm
I'll just eat it!
mmm
Mnh-mnh.
Mmm.
I can sleep. Good evening.
Thank you for the food.
It was so delicious.
It was so delicious that it made me forget this heat and fatigue.
The banana juice was great too.
Cycling, though,
But it was not as hard as I thought it would be.
I would like to take a bicycle again if I have a chance.
Red bike?
There are bicycles for rent in town.
I would like to start from there.
That's all for now, Hinasanbo.So, that's all for now.
To everyone watching, please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.
See you again sometime.
Is it a zatsukatsu? What is it?
Please subscribe to our channel.